F: Has it started?
T: Yes
F: Okay, wait.
F: I need to share my screen first.
F: Alright, everyone...
F: Hold on, where's the photo?
F: Ah, never mind.
F: Here it is.
F: Make me host. Whoever wants to screen share-
T: Yeah, hang on.
F: Nice stretching, Aldian.
T: Done.
F: Can you see this (screen)?
T: I can.
F: What do you see?
F: Do you see a picture?
T: Yes.
F: This is the original app (view).
F: This is the news list; news content...
F: Religious study list; and their contents...
F: Ask the cleric feature.
F: So we have made 2 alternative designs. Wait...
F: This is design 1.
F: Can you guys see it?
T, B, Y: Yes.
F: Ok.
F: So this is design 1's news list.
F: This is the news content view.
F: This is the ask a cleric feature.
F: This is the religious study list... this is the contents.
F: This is the ask a cleric form.
F: Next, we have...
F: Design 2.
F: This is design 2's news list.
F: This is the religious study list; and this is the news content; and religious study content.
F: This is ask a cleric form.
F: This is the ask a cleric page.
F: And this is the answer page.
F: You guys understand everything?
Everyone: Yeah.
F: Shall we start voting?
T: Can you put them side by side?
(Design 1 is in the middle)
(Design 2 is on the left)
(The original is on the right)
(News list)
(News content)
(Religious study list)
(Religious study contents)
(Ask the cleric feature)
F: In the original design, the QnA list are in another page. But in the alternative designs, we've decided to display them in that same page.
(QnA content)
(Question form)
F: I think that's all.
Everyone: Yes.
F: Let's start voting or...?
T: Sure.
F: You're recording this, right?
T: Yes.
F: So who wants to start first?
F: You go first.
T: Me?
F: Yes.
T: I vote design 1.
F: Ok, now Bagas?
B: Based on what you've shown me-
B: I think design 1 is quite static and acceptable
B: It has tabs that explain the pages.
B: On the other hand, design 2 makes the UI more appealing.
B: Design 2 makes the use seem more comfortable because of it and a short explanation text.
B: So, based on the user's comfort and (???) i vote design 2.
Y: For me, design 2 is the best. The view looks much better.
F: Oh, ok. Do you have any more to say?
Y: Hmm, not really. I didn't analyze it too deeply. But design 2 definitely looks more neat and clean. So it doesn't look boring.
B: Can i add something?
F: Sure.
B: The reason i picked design 2 is because of the purpose.
B: Usually (for apps like this) the user base consists mostly of old men.
B: They have bad eyesights because of their age.
B: So i think design 2 is perfect for people like them. It has pictures and explanation texts.
B: So it's easier for elderly people.
T: I voted for design 1 because it's easier to read.
T: If you look at design 2, the spaces between sentences are too close. That's all.
F: What were you saying, Yusriizal?
Y: I have the same reason as Bagas on why i picked design 2.
Y: In the picture of design 2, it clearly says "send" unlike design 1.
Y: This could be troublesome for some old people. There's a chance that they don't know the send button.
F: Oh, so it fits for boomers.
Y: Yeah, and-
Y: It goes the same for the button that returns you.